https://www.humanrightsattorney.com/privacy-policy/

CASE EVALUATION APPOINTMENTHomeAboutReviewsCase Evaluation AppointmentAttorney ReferralsPodcasts/VideosContact
Heather L. Poole, PC, Professional Law Corporation CASE EVALUATION APPOINTMENTTOLL FREE
1-877-486-2678 1.877 HUMAN-RTS Complex Family Issues & Removal Defense Complex Family Issues & Removal DefenseGreen Cards for SpousesConditional Green CardsLGBTQ+Fiancé VisasAbused ImmigrantsUnlawful Presence & Illegal Entries3 & 10 Year Bar WaiversMisrepresentationCriminal WaiversDeportation DefenseCitizenshipOther Visas & Green CardsPresident’s AnnouncementAttorney at Your CIS Interview Representing Clients All Over the U.S.About Attorney HeatherWhat We Stand ForSchedule a Case EvaluationUpcoming Immigration TalksMediaPrivacy Policy & Terms and ConditionsHire Attorney Heather NavigationAbout Attorney HeatherWhat We Stand ForSchedule a Case EvaluationUpcoming Immigration TalksMediaPrivacy Policy & Terms and ConditionsHire Attorney Heather About Attorney Heather
Click here Attorney Videos
Click here Referrals
Click here Upcoming Talks
Click hereGet Your Free Guide How to Hire
the Right
Immigration
Attorney
for Your Case. signupDon't Know Where to Start? Video
Privacy Policy & Terms and ConditionsPRIVACY POLICY & TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USING THIS SITEImmigration Attorney Heather L. Poole  is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website as well as potential and existing clients of our services and anyone providing us with their contact information. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or confidentiality, please send an e-mail to info@humanrightsattorney.com.Privacy PolicyWHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT? Attorney Heather L. Poole only collects user-provided personally identifiable information. This information is provided when website visitors complete one of our online forms (examples: general inquiry or consultation form). The following list includes ways we collect personal information from our website visitors and the type of information collected:  Required information varies depending on the form and at most includes (i) full name, (ii) e-mail address and (iii) phone number. The provision of this information is mandatory in order to receive a response from Attorney Heather L. Poole through our website. The provision of the remaining information requested on the case evaluation or consultation form is optional, although helpful in determining any available legal services to you.DO YOU SHARE MY INFORMATION?Attorney Heather L. Poole takes confidentiality and your privacy very seriously. We will not share, rent or sell your personally identifiable information with third parties. WHAT SECURITY MEASURES ARE TAKEN TO PROTECT MY INFORMATION?  All data from online communications is stored in a secured, password encrypted database and any print with personal information in our physical location is locked and available only to immediate staff directly supervised by the Attorney.  Attorney client/privilege forbids us from sharing your information with any third party without your permission, even for those who are not existing clients but may be consulting us for legal services.HOW DOES HEATHER L. POOLE, PC USE MY INFORMATION? Personal information collected by Attorney Heather L. Poole is used primarily for the purpose in which it is collected: to facilitate the distribution of a newsletter or proposal to interested recipients who have contacted us regarding legal services. We may also occasionally contact you to:To notify you of new information or legal services that may be of interest to you based on a change in the law; To send promotional materials and special offers; andTo conduct surveys or to obtain feedback on our servicesAll communication will be related and relevant to what you have requested.DO WE USE COOKIES OR WEB BUGS TO TRACK VISITORS? No.WHAT IF THERE ARE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY? If we change our Privacy and Spam Policy, we will post those changes on our privacy page under the “About Us” Page on this website, www.humanrightsattorney.com. If at any point we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice whether or not we use their information in this new manner. By default we will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.HOW CAN I OPT OUT? If you have opted in and later desire to opt-out from further receiving any contact from us via email, you can make this change at any time by sending an e-mail with UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line to info@humanrightsattorney.com. Be sure to use or indicate the e-mail address to be removed from the list.WEB LINKS: This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy and spam policies of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.HOW DO I CONTACT ATTORNEY HEATHER L. POOLE? If you have any further questions or comments regarding this website or this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at info@humanrightsattorney.com or at:Attorney Heather L. Poole, HEATHER L POOLE PC – Immigration Lawyers225 S. Lake Avenue, Suite 300, Pasadena CA 91101Telephone: 877.486.2678LEGAL DISCLAIMER: We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our site.Terms and Conditions of Accessing/Viewing/Using this Website TERMS1. By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.2. Use Licensea.     Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information) on HEATHER L. POOLE, PC’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:          i.        modify or copy the materials;         ii.        use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);        iii.        attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on HEATHER L. POOLE, PC’s web site;        iv.        remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or         v.        transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.b.    This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by HEATHER L. POOLE, PC at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.3. Disclaimera.     The materials on HEATHER L. POOLE, PC’s web site are provided “as is”. HEATHER L. POOLE, PC makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, HEATHER L. POOLE, PC does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.No attorney/client privilege or Attorney/Client relationship is established by view, use, or accessing the content on this site. Further, no legal advice is being given or offered by or should be implied by view or use of this website. Always consult a licensed, competent attorney about the facts of your particular case to determine what advice applies to you or may be followed. 4. LimitationsIn no event shall HEATHER L. POOLE, PC or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on HEATHER L. POOLE, PC’s Internet site, even if HEATHER L. POOLE, PC or a HEATHER L. POOLE, PC authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.5. Revisions and ErrataThe materials appearing on HEATHER L. POOLE, PC’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. HEATHER L. POOLE, PC does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. HEATHER L. POOLE, PC may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. HEATHER L. POOLE, PC does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials or guarantee in any form that the information provided in this website reflects current immigration agency or court legal procedures, legal updates, immigration caselaw, or state of federal or state immigration law.6. RefundsCase Evaluation Fees.  CANCELLATION/POSTPONEMENT POLICY: To cancel your case evaluation, you must do so more than 24 hours prior to your scheduled case evaluation to avoid being charged. This time slot is especially reserved for you. We allow one postponement with no charge if rescheduled more than 24 hours prior to your appointment.  Otherwise, there is no refund issue for any payment made for a case evaluation. Existing Clients:Legal Fees.  a. TERMINATION/CREDIT/REFUND policy.  The client may terminate the firm’s representation of client pursuant to the mutual agreed upon engagement at any time, without cause. Client will not be entitled to refund of legal fees received to that point for fees that have already been earned when client withdraws. Any unearned Legal Fees on retainer with HEATHER L. POOLE PC are refundable to the client once the client has notified HEATHER L. POOLE, PC in writing (with a wet-ink signature delivered via dated, paper request to HEATHER L. POOLE PC’s headquarters) that client wishes to terminate representation.   Client is not owed legal fees for work already earned by the “Attorney” (any practicing attorney acting on behalf of HEATHER L. POOLE, PC).  Fees “already earned” by the Attorney will be dictated by the hourly rate agreed upon in the engagement agreement by both parties and amount of time incurred on the case prior to termination.  The client understands and agrees that the firm also has the right and sometimes the obligation to terminate the engagement, on written notification to the client, if further representation interferes with the independent legal judgment of the Attorney, if the client is utilizing the Attorney’s services to commit an unlawful act, or if further representation otherwise is mandated pursuant to the Rules of Professional Conduct. b. Effect of Client’s Nonpayment (Breach): If Client selects the payment plan option, Client acknowledges that Attorney’s services are contingent upon client’s timely payments pursuant to this agreement. Client understands and agrees that Attorney has offered client a payment plan as a professional courtesy. Client agrees to make payments on time and Client further understands and agrees that Attorney shall not be bound to continue legal services if client fails to make timely payments. If client does not fulfill obligations as set forth in the engagement letter, then Firm has the option of withdrawing from representing client. If firm withdraws due to non payment, the Firm has no obligation to continue or renew representation of client.Attorney and the Client will use their best efforts in furthering the purposes of the engagement agreement. However, nothing in the engagement agreement or anything on this website or anything in Attorney’s statements to Client will be or should be construed in any shape or form to be a promise or guarantee about the legal outcome of Client’s matter. Attorney makes no such promises or guarantees, in accordance with Californialaw. If there is any disagreement or dispute between you and the firm concerning fees or any other claim relating to your matter which arises out of our representation ofyou, you and the firm hereby agree to submit such dispute to binding arbitration under Section 1280 of the Code of Civil Procedure of the State of California relating to arbitration of contract disputes. The prevailing party shall be entitled to reasonable attorney’s fees and costs incurred in such arbitration. Client and undersigned agree that this contract shall be governed and construed according to the law of California, which shall have exclusive jurisdiction in regard to matters arising from the Attorney/Client agreement. c. Conclusion of Legal Services: When Attorney’s services conclude, all unpaid chargesshall become immediately due and payable. After Attorney’s services conclude, Attorney will, upon Client’s request, deliver Client’s file to Client.  Attorney reserves the right to maintain the format of Client’s file, whether digital or written. 7. LinksHEATHER L. POOLE, PC has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by HEATHER L. POOLE, PC of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.8. Site Terms of Use ModificationsHEATHER L. POOLE, PC may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.9. Governing LawAny claim relating to HEATHER L. POOLE, PC’s web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions.General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.  SIGN UP FOR FREE IMMIGRATION UPDATESSubmitThanks for your information.We will get back to you soon.TOLL FREE
1-877-486-2678 1.877 HUMAN-RTSUseful LinksAbout HeatherContactCase Evaluation AppointmentClient ReviewsAttorney ReferralsPodcasts And VideoPrivacy Policy & Terms and ConditionsTerms of UseVideo SitemapImmigration OptionsGreen Cards for SpousesFiancé VisasConditional Green CardsAbused ImmigrantsUnlawful Presence & Illegal Entries3 & 10 Year Bar WaiversMisrepresentation WaiversCriminal WaiversOther Visas & Green CardsDeportation DefenseLGBTQ+Attorney at Your CIS InterviewHeather's Tool BarUpcoming TalksReferralsPodcasts & VideoFAQArticles and GuidesContact InfoHEATHER L. POOLE, PC225 S. Lake Avenue, Suite 300, Pasadena CA 91101Telephone: (Toll Free) 1.877.HUMAN-RTS (486-2678);E-mail: info@humanrightsattorney.com
As rated in
2020 Heather L. Poole, PC. All rights reserved.
